[{"answer": "Oops.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 43, "question": "Do you remember that?", "qSentId": 42}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "Steak sandwiches?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "Because I'm in love with Monica.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 75, "question": "And why not?", "qSentId": 74}, {"answer": "Everyone who ever walked on the set, I think --", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 86, "question": "You'd kissed everyone else?", "qSentId": 85}, {"answer": "No, no, not much.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "Do you watch?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "Yes, that's the neurosis.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "Why did I suck so much?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "Yes, no.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 149, "question": "You know?", "qSentId": 148}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 154, "question": "Would you want to change that or?", "qSentId": 153}, {"answer": "Oh, I would keep going.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 163, "question": "You would have kept going or you would have stopped?", "qSentId": 162}, {"answer": "Yes, I guess the ideology was that like we would decide if that would be better.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "But why not have fun until they do?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "I'm not used to -- yes --", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "You actually checked him, like really?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "-- was it hilarious I was supposed to say--", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "Hilarious?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "And -- yes, I do.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 214, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 213}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 238, "question": "You do?", "qSentId": 237}, {"answer": "All you need to succeed --", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 245, "question": "All you need to what?", "qSentId": 244}, {"answer": "-- to be appealing, to --", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "It is?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "On the show.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "Oh, yes?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "I love you so much.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 268, "question": "I thought you were going back?", "qSentId": 267}, {"answer": "Me.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 277, "question": "Who?", "qSentId": 276}, {"answer": "Maybe you haven't done it yet.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 280, "question": "You know, did you notice that?", "qSentId": 279}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "That I'm not there?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "Oh.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 304, "question": "It's called how well do you know your own project?", "qSentId": 303}, {"answer": "Well, $900 --", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "-- what we were making before?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "Good.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 358, "question": "How -- how is everything going over there?", "qSentId": 357}, {"answer": "They're both fantastic.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "Yes?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 373, "question": "-- get to be on?", "qSentId": 372}, {"answer": "-- that's exactly what the tag line is here.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 379, "question": "-- thing?", "qSentId": 378}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "Is that what you mean?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "UDROW: We have -- like I am not allowed to give too much away.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 397, "question": "-- interesting secrets that you've -- that you found out?", "qSentId": 396}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 412, "question": "Do you fake them?", "qSentId": 411}, {"answer": "I like it for \"Who Do You Think You Are?\"", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 428, "question": "Do you like being behind the scenes or in front?", "qSentId": 427}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "Which is just a -- it's -- those are just the words, the first letters for How Well Do You Know Your Own Project?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "-- I'm going to sign a copy of one of your DVDs for you and give it back to you.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "Yes?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "Well, that would be worth a lot, actually.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 461, "question": "Isn't that great?", "qSentId": 460}, {"answer": "I know that answer.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "What was the most successful one that got the most viewers?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "I mean I knew that answer.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "Do you?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 486, "question": "Your most successful, OK?", "qSentId": 485}, {"answer": "Oh, \"Web Therapy.\"", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 490, "question": "Do you think Meryl Streep is more proud of her performance in \"Web Therapy\" or \"Sophie's Choice\"?", "qSentId": 489}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 496, "question": "And plus, that movie, I didn't see that movie, but is that whole movie just her going -- that one?", "qSentId": 495}, {"answer": "There's a lot of other difficult stuff in it.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "It's -- so there's other stuff in that?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "OK?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "Oh, wow!", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "Do you know the name of the -- of the title of that episode, what that episode was called?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "I don't know the --", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 530}, {"answer": "That's right.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "That's right?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "ACK: Sure.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 593, "question": "So what's going on just with the body and the mind of an alcoholic?", "qSentId": 592}, {"answer": "ACK: Well, you know, Corey had been in treatment before.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 620, "question": "What could -- what could have been done?", "qSentId": 619}, {"answer": "Yes, well --", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 663, "question": "So this is for primarily -- it's for first time, non- violent drug offenders, correct?", "qSentId": 662}, {"answer": "Actually, it's -- it's for who are really pretty seriously engaged in the criminal justice system.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 667, "question": "-- but that's who it -- that's who it's for, primarily, right?", "qSentId": 666}, {"answer": "Well, 75 percent of our graduates never see another pair of handcuffs.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 673, "question": "And what is the success rate of drug court?", "qSentId": 672}, {"answer": "Well, it's a long story.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 693, "question": "How did you get from there to now here, sitting here on CNN?", "qSentId": 692}, {"answer": "I would say seek treatment.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 725, "question": "What do you think those guys should do?", "qSentId": 724}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 740, "question": "So -- but there is a little window that opens for people, right?", "qSentId": 739}, {"answer": "Well, there really are one of two camps.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 763, "question": "Who's not on the drug court side and what is their argument?", "qSentId": 762}, {"answer": "Well, in the past 24 years, we've saved a million people.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 778, "question": "How many people have we saved?", "qSentId": 777}, {"answer": "That is right.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 838, "question": "So, you now are a New York best-selling author, \"New York Times\" best selling author, is that right?", "qSentId": 837}, {"answer": "You know, every job is it's own animal, I guess, and you just sort of have to learn the world and the world of \"Gilmore Girls\" was musical and precise, and the world of \"Parenthood\" is more about a family and they want it to sound messy and overlap and they shot it in a way that we can do that.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 850, "question": "Do you like that better?", "qSentId": 849}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 877, "question": "Do you want to play a game?", "qSentId": 876}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 883, "question": "It's called, how well do you know your own project, OK?", "qSentId": 882}, {"answer": "Begin.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 890, "question": "What's the first word?", "qSentId": 889}, {"answer": "Yes -- no, it gives me the willies.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 901, "question": "Did you know that?", "qSentId": 900}, {"answer": "Fantastic.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 910, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 909}, {"answer": "Your book.", "docId": "130726pmt", "aSentId": 917, "question": "What do you win?", "qSentId": 916}]